Wolf, Benjamin H. Additional Arbitration Files 5539
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- 75-20 Federal Aviation Administration vs. Professional Air Traffic Controllers Association (PATCO), 1975 (Box 13, Folder 17)
  12/23/75. Routine Correspondence, Exhibits, Supporting Documents, Arbitrator's Notes, TR. Issue: Fringe Benefits--Travel Pay.
- 75-21 Rider College vs. American Association of University Professors, 1975 (Box 13, Folder 18)
  5/75. Routine Correspondence. Withdrawn
- 75-22 Jersey City State College vs. New Jersey State College Locals, American Federation of Teachers (AFT), 1975 (Box 13, Folder 19)
  6/30/75. Routine Correspondence, Exhibits, Arbitrator's Notes, TR. Issue: Rates of Pay--Increase--Calculation.
- 75-23 New York City Labor Relations vs. Detectives Endowment Association, 1975 (Box 13, Folder 20)
  5/75. Routine Correspondence, Exhibits, Supporting Documents, Arbitrator's Notes, TR. Issue: Assignment of Jobs--Assignment to Work Outside of Classification
- 75-24 Town of Greenburgh vs. Greenburgh Police Association, Civil Service Employees Association (CSEA), Local 860, 1975 (Box 13, Folder 21)
  10/75. Routine Correspondence. Withdrawn.
- 75-25 Long Island Railroad vs. United Transportation Union, Local 645, 1975 (Box 13, Folder 22)
  4/25/75. Routine Correspondence, Exhibits, Arbitrator's Notes. Issue: Suspension--Tardiness
- 75-26 Bellmore Merrick Board of Education vs. Secondary Teachers, 1975 (Box 13, Folder 23)
  6/75. Routine Correspondence. Settled
- 75-27 Kollsman Instrument Corporation vs. District 15, International Association of Machinists and Aerospace Workers (IAM), 1975 (Box 13, Folder 24)
  5/15/75. Routine Correspondence, Exhibits, Arbitrator's Notes, Agreements. Issue: Layoff--Seniority.
- 75-28 Westchester County vs. Civil Service Employees Association, Local 860, 1975 (Box 13, Folder 25)
  6/16/75. Routine Correspondence, Exhibits, Supporting Documents, Arbitrator's Notes. Issue: Rates of Pay--Recall--Time Not Worked.
- 75-29 Kean College vs. Council of New Jersey State College Locals, 1975 (Box 13, Folder 26)
  3/75. Routine Correspondence. Withdrawn
- 75-30 St. Francis Community Health vs. District 1199, National Union of Hospital and Health Care Employees, 1975 (Box 13, Folder 27)
  6/75. Routine Correspondence, Exhibits, Arbitrator's Notes. Issue: Rates of Pay--Shift Differential.
- 75-31 Mobil Chemical Company vs. Local 462, International Brotherhood of Teamsters (IBT), 1975 (Box 13, Folder 28)
  10/75. (No Award), Routine Correspondence, Exhibits, Arbitrator's Notes. Issue: Discharge--Absences, Excessive; Overtime.
- 75-32 Baker-Beach Nut Corporation vs. Local 697, Bakery and Confectionary Workers International, 1975 (Box 13, Folder 29)
  10/16/75. Routine Correspondence, Supporting Documents, Exhibits, Arbitrator's Notes, TR. Issue: Assignment of Jobs--Departmental Work.
- 75-34 State of New York Department of Motor Vehicles vs. Civil Service Employees Association, 1975 (Box 13, Folder 30)
  5/75. Routine Correspondence. Withdrawn.
- 75-35 Ryder Truck Lines, Incorporated vs. Local 707, International Brotherhood of Teamsters (IBT), 1975 (Box 13, Folder 31)
  6/6/75. Routine Correspondence, Exhibits, Arbitrator's Notes. Issue: Discharge--Theft of Company Property.
- 75-36 General Dynamics Corporation vs. International Union of Operating Engineers, Local 545, 1975 (Box 14, Folder 1)
  9/15/75. Routine Correspondence, Exhibits, Supporting Documents, Arbitrator's Notes. Issue: Layoff--Seniority.
- 75-37 Toms River Chemical Corporation vs. Oil, Chemical, and Atomic Workers International Union (OCAW), 8-562, 1975 (Box 14, Folder 2)
- 75-38 County of Erie vs. Faculty Federation of Erie Community Colleges, 1975 (Box 14, Folder 3)
- 75-39 New York State (Mental Hygiene) vs. Civil Service Employees Association (CSEA), 1975 (Box 14, Folder 4)
  6/75. Routine Correspondence. Settled.
- 75-40 Jersey State College vs. Council of New Jersey State College Locals, American Federation of Teachers (AFT), Ruth Reardon, 1975 (Box 14, Folder 5)
  6/26/75. Routine Correspondence, Exhibits, Arbitrator's Notes, TR. Issue: Promotion--Failure To Qualify
- 75-41 Kean College (New Jersey) vs. Council of New Jersey State College Locals, American Federation of Teachers (AFT), 1975 (Box 14, Folder 6)
  9/8/75. Routine Correspondence, Exhibits, Arbitrator's Notes, TR. Issue: Discrimination--Age.
- 75-42 Kuhn and Jacob Company vs. United Rubber, Cork, Linoleum, and Plastic Workers of America, 1975 (Box 14, Folder 7)
  5/75. Routine Correspondence, Arbitrator's Notes. Physical Disability--Termination Following.
- 75-43 Star Case Company vs. District 65, Distributive Workers, 1975 (Box 14, Folder 8)
- 75-44 Committee of Interns and Residents vs. City of New York, 1975 (Box 14, Folder 9)
  6/30/75. Routine Correspondence, Exhibits, Arbitrator's Notes, TR. Issue: Dual Employment--Management Rights.
- 75-45 Professional Staff Association vs. New York State United Teachers, Incorporated, 1975 (Box 14, Folder 10)
  8/4/75. Routine Correspondence, Exhibits, Supporting Documents, Arbitrator's Notes. Issue: Fringe Benefits--Health Insurance; Sick Leave
- 75-46 DeLaval Turbine, Incorporated vs. United Steelworkers of America, Local 3355, 1975 (Box 14, Folder 11)
  8/75. Routine Correspondence. Cancelled
- 75-47 Pall Trinity Micro Corporation vs. United, Automobile, Aerospace, and Agricultural Implement Workers of America (UAW), Local 1326, 1975 (Box 14, Folder 12)
  7/28/75. Routine Correspondence, Exhibits, Supporting Documents, Arbitrator's Notes. Issue: Rates of Pay--Assignment of Jobs--Classification of Jobs
- 75-48 State of New York (Mental Hygiene) vs. Civil Service Employees Association (CSEA), 1975 (Box 14, Folder 13)
  5/30/75. Routine Correspondence, Arbitrator's Notes. Issue: Discipline--Improper Personal Conduct--Detrimental Conduct.
- 75-49 Jersey City College (Speigel) vs. Council of New Jersey State College Locals, American Federation of Teachers (AFT), 1975 (Box 14, Folder 14)
  7/21/75. Routine Correspondence, Arbitrator's Notes, Exhibits, TR. Issue: Termination of Employment--Failure to Qualify for Promotion.
- 75-50 State of New Jersey, Kean College (Myers) vs. Council of New Jersey State College Locals, 1976 (Box 14, Folder 15)
  3/15/76. Routine Correspondence, Exhibits, Supporting Documents, Transcripts, Arbitrator's Notes. Issue: Termination of Employment--Discrimination.
- 75-51 National Cash Register vs. International Association of Machinists and Aerospace Workers (IAMAW), Local 1607, 1975 (Box 14, Folder 16)
  9/22/75. Routine Correspondence, Exhibits, Arbitrator's Notes. Issue: Classification of Jobs--Evaluation of Job Factors
- 75-52 National Cash Register vs. Railway and Airline Clerks Local 1932, 1975 (Box 14, Folder 17)
  8/25/75. Routine Correspondence, Exhibits, Arbitrator's Notes, TR. Issue: Rates of Pay--Increase
- 75-53 New York City Office Labor Relations vs. American Federation of State, County, and Municipal Employees (AFSCME), District Council 37, 1975 (Box 14, Folder 18)
  5/75. (No Award), Routine Correspondence, Arbitrator's Notes. Issue: Classification of Jobs
- 75-54 J.N. Futia Company, Incorporated vs. International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers (IBEW), Local 438, 1975 (Box 14, Folder 19)
  8/14/75. Routine Correspondence, Supporting Documents, Exhibits, Arbitrator's Notes. Issue: Assignment of Jobs--Bargaining Unit Work.
- 75-55 Beth Abraham Hospital vs. District 1199, 1975 (Box 14, Folder 20)
  6/75. Routine Correspondence. Cancelled
- 75-56 Hughes Airwest vs. Aircraft Mechanics Fraternal Association, Local 32, 1975 (Box 14, Folder 21)
  7/75. Routine Correspondence. Withdrawn
- 75-57 Simmons Company vs. International Association of Machinists and Aerospace Workers (IAMAW), District 15, Local 315, 1975 (Box 14, Folder 22)
  8/12/75. Routine Correspondence, Exhibits, Arbitrator's Notes. Issue: Layoff--Remedy for Improper Layoff.
- 75-58 Southwestern Bell Telephone vs. Communication Workers of America, 1975 (Box 14, Folder 23)
  9/75. Routine Correspondence. Settled
- 75-59 BASF Wyandotte Corporation vs. International Chemical Workers Union No. 846, 1975 (Box 14, Folder 24)
  9/16/75. Routine Correspondence, Exhibits, Supporting Documents, Arbitrator's Notes. Issue: Overtime--Distribution.
- 75-60 Multi-Metal Wire Cloth vs. United Automobile, Aerospace, and Agricultural Implement Workers of America (UAW), Local 365, 1975 (Box 14, Folder 25)
  9/18/75. Routine Correspondence, Exhibits, Arbitrator's Notes. Issue: Discipline Warnings.
- 75-61 New York State Police vs. Police Benevolent Association, 1975 (Box 14, Folder 26)
  7/75. Routine Correspondence. Cancelled.
- 75-62 Orange County Boxes vs. Orange County Boxes Teachers Association, 1975 (Box 14, Folder 27)
  7/25/75. Routine Correspondence, Exhibits, Arbitrator's Notes, (Impasse). Issue: Rates of Pay--Fringe Benefits--Schedules of Work; Leaves of Absence
- 75-63 Hamilton Standard, United Technologies vs. International Association of Machinists and Aerospace Workers (IAMAW), Local 743, 1975 (Box 14, Folder 28)
  12/11/75. Routine Correspondence, Exhibits, Supporting Documents, Transcripts, Arbitrator's Notes. Issue: Discharge--Absences; Excessive
- 75-64 Dry Harbor Nursing Home vs. District 1199, 1975 (Box 14, Folder 29)
  6/23/75. Routine Correspondence, Exhibits, Arbitrator's Notes. Issue: Discharge--Improper Job Attitude; Tardiness.
- 75-65 Pepsi-Cola Newburgh Bottling vs. Local 812, Soft Drink Workers, International Brotherhood of Teamsters (IBT), 1976 (Box 15, Folder 1)
  1/76. Routine Correspondence. Withdrawn.
- 75-66 Town of Greenburgh vs. Civil Service Employees Association (CSEA), 1975 (Box 15, Folder 2)
  7/8/75. Routine Correspondence, Arbitrator's Notes, Agreements. Issue: Discharge--Apprentice--Contract Interpretation.
- 75-67 Greenport School District vs. Greenport Teachers' Association, 1975 (Box 15, Folder 3)
  7/28/75. Routine Correspondence, Exhibits, Arbitrator's Notes. Issue: Termination of Employment--Probationary Employees.
- 75-68 Montclair State (Van Benscholen) vs. Council of New Jersey State College Locals, 1975 (Box 15, Folder 4)
- 75-69 Montclair State (Brook) vs. Council of New Jersey State College Locals, 1975 (Box 15, Folder 5)
  7/75. (No Award), Routine Correspondence, Arbitrator's Notes, Exhibits. Issue: Rates of Pay--Classification of Job.
- 75-70 Anheuser-Busch Incorporated vs. International Brotherhood of Teamsters (IBT), Local 153, 1975 (Box 15, Folder 6)
  8/75. Routine Correspondence. Withdrawn
- 75-71 William Patterson College (Luskin) vs. Council of New Jersey State College Locals, 1975 (Box 15, Folder 7)
  10/23/75. Routine Correspondence, Exhibits, Supporting Documents, Arbitrator's Notes, TR. Issue: Discrimination--Termination of Job.
- 75-72 Bivins Freight Service vs. International Brotherhood of Teamsters, Local 676, 1975 (Box 15, Folder 8)
  10/75. Routine Correspondence. Settled
- 75-74 Ramapo College (Peck) vs. Council of New Jersey State College Local, 1975 (Box 15, Folder 9)
  8/75. Routine Correspondence. Settled.
- 75-75 William Patterson College (Green), State of New Jersey vs. Council of New Jersey State College Locals, American Federation of Teachers (AFT), 1976 (Box 15, Folder 10)
  2/23/76. Routine Correspondence, Exhibits, Transcripts, Arbitrator's Notes. Issue: Termination of Employment--Failure to Qualify for Promotion
- 75-76 Levin Fixtures Corporation vs. United Brotherhood of Carpenters and Joiners, Local 2682, 1975 (Box 15, Folder 11)
  8/7/75. Routine Correspondence, Exhibits, Arbitrator's Notes. Issue: Layoff--Recall.
- 75-77 Curtin Matheson Scientific vs. International Brotherhood of Teamsters (IBT), Local 560, 1975 (Box 15, Folder 12)
  11/10/75. Routine Correspondence, Exhibits, Arbitrator's Notes. Issue: Discharge--Fights and Altercations.
- 75-78 William Patterson College (Heller) vs. Council of New Jersey State College Locals, 1976 (Box 15, Folder 13)
  1/29/76. Routine Correspondence, Exhibits, Transcripts, Arbitrator's Notes. Issue: Termination--Failure to Qualify for Promotion.
- 75-79 New York City Off-Track Betting vs. Local 2021, District Council 37, American Federation of State, County, and Municipal Employees (AFSCME), 1975 (Box 15, Folder 14)
  10/30/75. Routine Correspondence, Exhibits, Arbitrator's Notes. Issue: Assignment of Jobs--Assignment to Work Outside Classification.
- 75-80 New York State (Mental Hygiene Department) vs. Civil Service Employees Association (CSEA) (Perry), 1975 (Box 15, Folder 15)
  7/75. Routine Correspondence. Postponed
- 75-81 New York State (Mental Hygiene Department) vs. Civil Service Employees Association (CSEA), 1975 (Box 15, Folder 16)
- 75-82 Peter J. Schweitzer Division vs. United Papermakers International Union (UPIU), Local 1482, 1975 (Box 15, Folder 17)
  1/24/75. Routine Correspondence, Exhibits, Arbitrator's Notes. Issue: Physical Disability--Fringe Benefits--Insurance.
- 75-83 Trans World Airlines vs. Airline Pilots Association, 1975 (Box 15, Folder 18)
  12/75. Routine Correspondence. Settled.
- 75-84 Mt. Pleasant Central School District vs. Mt. Pleasant Teachers Association, 1975 (Box 15, Folder 19)
  11/20/75. Routine Correspondence, Exhibits, Supporting Documents, Arbitrator's Notes. Issue: Leaves of Absence--Sick Leave and Sick Pay.
- 75-85 Scott Paper Company vs. United Paperworkers International, 1975 (Box 15, Folder 20)
  10/2/75. Routine Correspondence, Exhibits, Arbitrator's Notes. Issue: Sick Leave--Termination Following Leave.
- 75-86 Boise Cascade Incorporated vs. Oswego Textile Workers' Union of America (TWUA) - AFL-CIO, 1976 (Box 15, Folder 21)
  1/76. RD. Cancelled
- 75-87 City of Syracuse vs. American Federation of State, County, and Municipal Employees (AFSCME), Council 66, 1975 (Box 15, Folder 22)
  9/75. Routine Correspondence. Cancelled
- 75-88 Weston Instruments Incorporated vs. Weston Employees Union, 1975 (Box 15, Folder 23)
  10/75. Routine Correspondence. Cancelled
- 75-89 New York State Division of New York State Police (Pasquale) vs. Police Benevolent Association, 1975 (Box 15, Folder 24)
  11/24/75. Routine Correspondence, Exhibits, Supporting Documents, Arbitrator's Notes, Agreements. Issue: Transfers--Seniority.
- 75-90 Dairylea vs. International Brotherhood of Teamsters (IBT), Local 338, 1975 (Box 15, Folder 25)
  10/28/75. Routine Correspondence, Exhibits, Supporting Documents, Arbitrator's Notes. Issue: Discharge--Tardiness, excessive.
- 75-91 Ellenville Board of Education vs. Ellenville Teachers' Association, 1975 (Box 15, Folder 26)
  12/19/75. Routine Correspondence, Exhibits, Supporting Documents, Arbitrator's Notes. Issue: Discharge--Probationary Employees--Contract Interpretation
- 75-92 Exxon Company vs. International Brotherhood of Teamsters (IBT), Local 877, 1976 (Box 15, Folder 27)
  3/22/76. Routine Correspondence, Supporting Documents, Exhibits, Arbitrator's Notes, TR. Issue: Discharge--Leaving Plant Without Permission.
- 75-93 Ford Printing Company vs. Printing Pressmen and Assistants Local 70, 1975 (Box 15, Folder 28)
  11/11/75. Routine Correspondence, Exhibits, Supporting Documents, Arbitrator's Notes, TR. Issue: Work-week--Decrease.
- 75-94 Kean College (D.W. Jones) vs. Council of New Jersey State College Locals, 1975 (Box 15, Folder 29)
  8/75. Routine Correspondence. Withdrawn.
- 75-95 Kean College (Schumacher) vs. Council of New Jersey State College Locals, 1975 (Box 15, Folder 30)
- 75-96 Old London Foods (Borden) vs. Local 338, Retail, Wholesale, and Department Store Union, 1975 (Box 15, Folder 31)
- 75-97 Middletown Board of Education vs. Middletown Teachers' Association, 1975 (Box 15, Folder 32)
  9/29/75. Routine Correspondence, Exhibits, Agreement, Arbitrator's Notes. Issue: Assignment of Jobs--Assignment of Work Outside Unit
- 75-98 Coast Metals vs. United Automobile, Aerospace, and Agricultural Implement Workers of America (UAW), Local 669, 1975 (Box 15, Folder 33)
  10/6/75. Routine Correspondence, Exhibits, Arbitrator's Notes. Issue: Classification of Jobs--Combination of Classifications--Contract Interpretation
- 75-99 County of Westchester vs. Civil Service Employees Association (CSEA), 1976 (Box 15, Folder 34)
  3/18/76. Routine Correspondence, Exhibits, Supporting Documents, Arbitrator's Notes. Issue: Demotions--Unsatisfactory Progress.
- 75-100 Port Washington Public Schools vs. Port Washington Teachers' Association, 1974 (Box 15, Folder 35)
  6/4/74. Routine Correspondence, Exhibits, Supporting Documents, Transcripts, Arbitrator's Notes. Issue: Timeliness--Arbitration; Grievance Procedure
- 75-101 New York City Board of Elections, Office of Labor Relations vs. Communication Workers of America, Local 1183, 1976 (Box 15, Folder 36)
  4/8/76. Routine Correspondence, Exhibits, Supporting Documents, Transcripts, Arbitrator's Notes. Issue: Schedules of Work--Overtime--Refusal of Overtime.
- 75-102 Good Humor Corporation vs. Milk Drivers and Dairy Employees, 1975 (Box 16, Folder 1)
  10/20/75. Routine Correspondence, Exhibits, Arbitrator's Notes. Issue: Discharge--Strikes, work stoppage--Improper Job Attitude
- 75-103 New York State Mental Hygiene Department (Letchworth Village) vs. Civil Service Employees Association (CSEA), Local 412, 1975 (Box 16, Folder 2)
  9/29/75. Routine Correspondence, Exhibits, Arbitrator's Notes. Issue: Discipline--Improper Personal Conduct--Sleeping on the Job
- 75-104 Trust Company of New Jersey vs. Local No. 142, Office and Professional Employees International Union, 1975 (Box 16, Folder 3)
  10/30/75. Routine Correspondence, Exhibits, Arbitrator's Notes. Issue: Union Business--Dues; Check-Off.
- 75-105 Pennwalt Corporation, Wallace and Tierman Division vs. International Union of Electrical, Radio, and Machine Workers (IUE), Local 370, 1976 (Box 16, Folder 4)
  5/25/76. Routine Correspondence, Exhibits, Supporting Documents, Arbitrator's Notes. Issue: Discrimination--Promotion--Vacancies.
- 75-106 Alpine Industries vs. Local 100, Service Employees International Union (SEIU), 1975 (Box 16, Folder 5)
  10/75. Cancelled
- 75-107 State of New York (Mental Hygiene Department) (Spraggins) vs. Civil Service Employees Association (CSEA), 1975 (Box 16, Folder 6)
  9/25/75. Routine Correspondence, Exhibits, Arbitrator's Notes. Issue: Discipline--Improper Personal Conduct--Alcoholism.
- 75-108 State of New York (Mental Hygiene Department) (Walters) vs. Civil Service Employees Association, 1975 (Box 16, Folder 7)
  10/14/75. Routine Correspondence, Exhibits, Arbitrator's Notes. Issue: Termination of Employment--Misconduct--Fights and Altercations; Absences--Excessive.
- 75-109 International Paper Company vs. United Paperworkers International Union (UPIU), 1975 (Box 16, Folder 8)
- 75-110 Anheuser Busch, Incorporated vs. International Brotherhood of Teamsters (IBT), Local 843, 1976 (Box 16, Folder 9)
  4/15/76. Routine Correspondence, Exhibits, Supporting Documents, Transcripts, Arbitrator's Notes. Issue: Suspension--Unsatisfactory Work.
- 75-111 Suffolk Company vs. Suffolk County Civil Service Employees Association (CSEA), 1975 (Box 16, Folder 10)
  12/75. (No Award), Routine Correspondence, Agreement, Arbitrator's Notes. Issue: Rates of Pay--Physical Disability.
- 75-112 Personal Products Company vs. United Paperworkers International Union, Local 536, 1975 (Box 16, Folder 11)
  11/75. Routine Correspondence. Settled.
- 75-113 Breneman, Incorporated vs. Textile Workers Oswego Joint County Board, 1976 (Box 16, Folder 12)
  1/26/76. Routine Correspondence, Exhibits, Supporting Documents, Arbitrator's Notes. Issue: Discharge--Improper Personal Conduct--Toward Supervisor.
- 75-114 Trans World Airlines vs. Air Line Pilots Association, 1975 (Box 16, Folder 13)
  11/75. Routine Correspondence. Postponed.
- 75-115 State of New Jersey (Ramapo-Roth) vs. Counsel of New Jersey State College Locals, American Federation of Teachers (AFT), 1976 (Box 16, Folder 14)
  1/12/76. Routine Correspondence, Supporting Documents, Exhibits, Agreement, Arbitrator's Notes, TR. Issue: Promotion--Failure To Qualify.
- 75-116 Board of Education of Hazlet Township vs. Hazlet Teachers' Association, 1976 (Box 16, Folder 15)
  5/4/76. Routine Correspondence, Supporting Documents, Exhibits, Agreement, Arbitrator's Notes. Issue: Work Week--Work Day--Change.
- 75-117 Johns Manville Products Corporation vs. United Paperworkers International Union (UPIU), Local 800, 1975 (Box 16, Folder 16)
  10/75. Routine Correspondence. Settled.
- 75-118 Shell Oil Company vs. Oil, Chemical, and Atomic Workers International Union (OCAWIU), Local 8-800, 1975 (Box 16, Folder 17)
  12/75. Routine Correspondence. Settled
- 75-119 Westvaco Corporation vs. United Paperworkers International, Local 1340, 1976 (Box 16, Folder 18)
  4/7/76. Routine Correspondence, Exhibits, Supporting Documents, Arbitrator's Notes. Issue: Rates of Pay--Holiday Pay--Overtime.
- 75-120 Kayser Roth Shoes vs. International Brotherhood of Teamsters, Local 660, 1976 (Box 16, Folder 19)
  2/76. Routine Correspondence. Withdrawn
- 75-121 Mineola Union Free School vs. Mineola Teachers, 1976 (Box 16, Folder 20)
  6/76. (No Award), Routine Correspondence, Exhibits, Arbitrator's Notes. Issue: Timeliness; Contracts--Expired, Grievances--Multiple Grievances.
- 75-122 New York City Health and Hospitals vs. Committee of Interns and Residents, 1976 (Box 16, Folder 21)
  1/76. (No Award), Routine Correspondence, Supporting Documents, Agreement, Arbitrator's Notes. Issue: Rates of Pay--Pay Periods.
- 75-123 TRW/UTC Transformers (Friscia) vs. Local 431, International Union of Electrical, Radio, and Machine Workers (IUE), 1975 (Box 16, Folder 22)
  12/75. (No Award), Routine Correspondence. Issue: Suspension.
- 75-124 TRW/UTC Transformers (Inventory) vs. Local 431, International Union of Electrical, Radio, and Machine Workers (IUE), 1976 (Box 16, Folder 23)
  1/15/76. Routine Correspondence, Exhibits, Arbitrator's Notes. Issue: Shutdown--Inventory
- 75-125 State of New York (Corrections) vs. Security and Law Enforcement Employees, 1975 (Box 16, Folder 24)
  11/75. Routine Correspondence. Settled
- 75-126 U.S. Metals Refining Company vs. United Steelworkers of America, Local 837, 1976 (Box 16, Folder 25)
  3/76. Routine Correspondence. Withdrawn.
- 75-127 New Jersey Bell Telephone Company vs. United Telephone Workers, 1976 (Box 16, Folder 26)
  1/76. Routine Correspondence. Withdrawn
- 75-128 Burndy Corporation vs. International Molders Local 84, 1976 (Box 16, Folder 27)
  1/76. (No Award), Routine Correspondence, Exhibits, Arbitrator's Notes. Issue: Contract Interpretation--Layoff--Temporary.
- 75-129 WBEN Incorporated vs. National Association of Broadcast Employees and Technicians (NABET), AFL-CIO, 1976 (Box 16, Folder 28)
  1/76. Routine Correspondence. Settled
- 75-130 Owens-Illinois, Incorporated vs. United Paperworkers International Union, Local 300, 1976 (Box 16, Folder 29)
  2/9/76. Routine Correspondence, Exhibits, Supporting Documents, Arbitrator's Notes. Issue: Overtime--Cancelled--Notice.
- 75-131 New York State (SUNY) vs. United University Professions, Incorporated, 1976 (Box 16, Folder 30)
  4/29/76. Routine Correspondence, Exhibits, Supporting Documents, Arbitrator's Notes. Issue: Contract Interpretation.
- 75-132 New Jersey Bell Telephone vs. Telephone Workers of New Jersey, 1976 (Box 16, Folder 31)
  9/2/76. Routine Correspondence, Exhibits, Supporting Documents, Transcripts, Arbitrator's Notes. Issue: Discharge--Absences, excessive.
- 75-133 National Broadcasting Company vs. Directors Guild of America, 1976 (Box 16, Folder 32)
  2/76. Routine Correspondence. Postponed
- 75-134 New York State Department of Correctional Services (Corrections-Brunswick) vs. Civil Service Employees Association (CSEA), 1976 (Box 16, Folder 33)
  1/5/76. Routine Correspondence, Exhibits, Supporting Documents, Arbitrator's Notes. Issue: Discharge--Absences, Excessive; Misconduct; Incompetence.